<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[ALSET@NUS]]></title><description><![CDATA[ALSET@NUS]]></description><link>http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public/</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 10:06:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Alset releases 2018 Annual Report]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Institute for the Application of Learning Science and Educational Technology (ALSET) is pleased to announce the release of its 201…]]></description><link>http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//ALSET-releases-AR2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//ALSET-releases-AR2018/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The Institute for the Application of Learning Science and Educational Technology (ALSET) is pleased to announce the release of its 2018 Annual Report. &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.nus.edu.sg/alsetnus/files/2019/01/2018-ALSET-Annual-Report-2auzh51.pdf&quot;&gt;Click here to download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded with the mission to build a community of researchers and educators at NUS with a shared passion for educational research and innovation, ALSET achieved many milestones this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Highlights of 2018.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community: we tripled the size of our research community, which now includes over 60 members from more than 15 unique disciplines, making us one of the most multidisciplinary institutes focused on the learning sciences and educational technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research: we launched exciting studies to investigate learning policies and practices in Singapore and around the world, with ongoing research projects covering topics as varied as the impact of sleep on learning; how social networks make you smarter (or dumber); and the undergraduate behaviours that not only help students to land a job, but also to build a successful career and a meaningful life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Courses: we ran courses and competitions that reached thousands of Singaporeans, including Learning to Learn Better and Learning to Choose Better, two new courses that help to cultivate essential skills in effective learning and decisions making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data: we bolstered the ALSET Educational Data Lake, a powerful resource that now includes anonymised data on over 120,000 NUS students and alumni, and which will help establish NUS as a global hub for educational research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alset partners with SkillsFuture Singapore to leverage AI for Career Guidance]]></title><description><![CDATA[On October 24, the Institute for Application of Learning Science and Educational Technology (ALSET) at the National University of Singapore…]]></description><link>http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//Alset-partners-SkillsFutureSingapore/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//Alset-partners-SkillsFutureSingapore/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;On October 24, the Institute for Application of Learning Science and Educational Technology (ALSET) at the National University of Singapore concluded a grant agreement with the Workforce Development Applied Research Fund (WDARF) at SkillsFuture Singapore to develop AI-based tools that support course selection and career planning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The grant will fund a pilot study to prototype an AI-driven recommender system that helps working adults in Singapore to identify courses that support continuing education goals. The study is intended as the initial phase of a long-term initiative by ALSET to research lifelong learning behaviours and policies in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This grant represents an exciting step in a broader journey to explore the power of new technologies to support lifelong learning and workforce resilience,” said Prof Robert Kamei, Director of ALSET and co-PI on the grant. “We see vast potential for technology to help working adults to navigate an increasingly competitive and complex job market, but we need to rigorously test and evaluate these technologies to ensure they achieve meaningful impact for workers of all backgrounds, not just those who already possess high-demand skills.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pilot study was unofficially launched in June and began with an analysis of SSG’s SkillsFuture Credit (SFC) Programme, which offers direct subsidies of S$500 to all Singapore citizens over the age of 25 for a pre-approved list of courses (and even higher subsidies for mid-career professionals). About 285,000 Singaporeans have used these credits since the programme was launched in 2016, providing a rich trove of anonymised data for understanding course selection behaviours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this analysis, ALSET is developing a recommender system that uses data on SFC credit claims and other various parameters, such as demographic and behavioural information, to recommend courses from the SFC catalogue. The system will be embedded in a mobile application under development by CXS International, a learning analytics company with a focus on preparing national workforces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The system will be tested on a cohort of NUS alumni between the ages of 22-29 starting in the fourth quarter of 2018, with final results expected in mid-2019. ALSET intends to use the findings to inform subsequent phases of research that involve the adaptation of this recommender system to other contexts, as well as broader research on the various factors that drive lifelong learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Recent advances in AI are well suited to the challenges of course recommendation and career guidance,” said Prof Min-Yen Kan, an Associate Professor at the NUS School of Computing, Deputy Director of ALSET’s Discovery Research Unit, and co-PI on the grant. “Using methodologies like collaborative filtering and natural language analysis, we are optimistic that our research will support the creation of impactful technologies.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These efforts dovetail with similar projects underway at NUS. The NUS School of Computing, for example, recently partnered with JobTech, a Singapore-based startup that provides data-driven job matching and labour market intelligence services, to develop NUS Career+, an AI-driven mobile app that advises students on education planning and career selection. Funded through AI Singapore’s 100 Experiments Programme, we expect this project will produce insights and technologies that complement ALSET’s research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As governments and educational institutions around the world increasingly understand the importance of lifelong learning for workforce resilience, ALSET looks forward to forging partnerships that produce new educational technologies and evaluate their impact. Please contact us if you are interested in learning more about our work in this field.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alset Mid-semester Update]]></title><description><![CDATA[As we enter the second half of the semester at NUS, we’d like to share a few updates on our progress and forthcoming initiatives at ALSET…]]></description><link>http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//alset-Midsemester-Update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//alset-Midsemester-Update/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;As we enter the second half of the semester at NUS, we’d like to share a few updates on our progress and forthcoming initiatives at ALSET.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, we recently welcomed Ranga Krishnan (Dean of Rush Medical College in Chicago) and Trevor Robbins (Professor of Cognitive Neuroscience and Experimental Psychology at Cambridge University) to NUS for our annual advisory board meeting in September. As always, they provided helpful feedback for our Research Theme Leaders, as well as ALSET Core Faculty member Paul O’Keefe, who joined the meeting to present his exciting new work on motivational mindsets and the cultivation of interests (check out recent coverage in &lt;a href=&quot;https://hbr.org/2018/09/having-a-growth-mindset-makes-it-easier-to-develop-new-interests&quot;&gt;HBR&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2018/07/find-your-passion-is-terrible-advice/564932/&quot;&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/a&gt; for more info).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As some of you may remember, Ranga’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.duke-nus.edu.sg/tags/dean-ranga-krishnan&quot;&gt;writings on the science of learning&lt;/a&gt; during his time as Dean of Duke-NUS Medical School were a major inspiration for the founding of ALSET. While he moved to the United States in 2015, he will be returning to Singapore again as the guest of honor for the Inaugural Science of Learning Symposium on Nov 2. It should be a great day of discussion, so we encourage you to join if you are available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of our work at ALSET involves creating and delivering courses that help learners to learn better. One recent effort from our Educational Unit was the launch of ALS1020 (Learning to Choose), a new course on the fundamentals of decision making and cognitive bias. We are pleased to report that we attracted 92 students for the first round of enrollment, and look forward to extending our reach in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ALSET courses not only provide meaningful learning experiences to students—they also serve as a lab for our researchers to investigate learning behaviors and test pedagogical interventions. One of those researchers is Joshua Gooley, who is currently using wearable sleep sensors to conduct research on student sleep habits in Learning to Learn Better, our flagship course on learning science. We welcome other researchers to partner with us for studies like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other research news, our Discovery Research Unit added 12 new researchers and 3 new research assistants to our team this semester. We also saw growth in the new Special Interest Group for Translational Classroom Research headed by Laksh Samavedham, who will be driving initiatives to improve our education programs using insights from the ALSET Educational Data Lake. They will benefit from our growing data assets, which are being managed by Chris Boesch and Kevin Hartman at our Translational Research Unit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.nus.edu.sg/alsetnus/2018/10/08/alset-opens-registration-ace-of-coders-2018/&quot;&gt;opened registration for Ace of Coders 2018&lt;/a&gt;, an annual ALSET-led coding event open to all secondary, junior college, and polytechnic students in Singapore. As in previous years, we expect to attract over 1000 students. It follows on a recent series of ALSET workshops for young females with an interest in learning to code. A major goal for these events is to better understand the barriers for entry and increase diversity in the STEM disciplines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still open to recruiting more faculty from across the university to join our growing research community, as well as external collaborators from near and far. If anyone you know is interested, please contact our Discovery Research Coordinator Alex Biotteau for details on the benefits and levels of membership available. For further information, you can also visit the ALSET Website or reach out to any of us directly.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[About]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is a demo site of the  HeroBlog , a  GatsbyJS  starter. Features: Easy editable content in  Markdown  files (posts, pages and parts…]]></description><link>http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//about/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is a demo site of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/greglobinski/gatsby-starter-hero-blog&quot;&gt;HeroBlog&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.org/&quot;&gt;GatsbyJS&lt;/a&gt; starter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Features:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easy editable content in &lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt; files (posts, pages and parts)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSS&lt;/strong&gt; with &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;styled-jsx&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;PostCSS&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEO&lt;/strong&gt; (sitemap generation, robot.txt, meta and OpenGraph Tags)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social&lt;/strong&gt; sharing (Twitter, Facebook, Google, LinkedIn)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comments&lt;/strong&gt; (Facebook)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Images&lt;/strong&gt; lazy loading and &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;webp&lt;/code&gt; support (gatsby-image)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post &lt;strong&gt;categories&lt;/strong&gt; (category based post list)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full text &lt;strong&gt;searching&lt;/strong&gt; (Algolia)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact&lt;/strong&gt; form (Netlify form handling)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSS&lt;/strong&gt; feed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% &lt;strong&gt;PWA&lt;/strong&gt; (manifest.webmanifest, offline support, favicons)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google &lt;strong&gt;Analytics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;App &lt;strong&gt;favicons&lt;/strong&gt; generator (node script)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easy customizable base &lt;strong&gt;styles&lt;/strong&gt; via &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;theme&lt;/code&gt; object generated from &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;yaml&lt;/code&gt; file (fonts, colors, sizes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React &lt;strong&gt;v.16&lt;/strong&gt; (gatsby-plugin-react-next)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Components&lt;/strong&gt; lazy loading (social sharing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ESLint&lt;/strong&gt; (google config)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prettier&lt;/strong&gt; code styling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Webpack &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;BundleAnalyzerPlugin&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Success]]></title><description><![CDATA[Thank you.  
I will answer to your message as soon as possible.]]></description><link>http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//success/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://nus.edu.sg/alset/public//success/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;
I will answer to your message as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>